<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container version="2">
  <Name>Jellyfin-Rewind</Name>
  <Repository>chaphasilor/jellyfin-rewind:latest</Repository>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/</Registry>
  <Network>bridge</Network>
  <MyIP/>
  <Shell>sh</Shell>
  <Privileged>false</Privileged>
  <Support>https://forums.unraid.net/topic/183068-support-grafgenixs-jellyfin-rewind/</Support>
  <Project>https://github.com/Chaphasilor/jellyfin-rewind</Project>
  <Overview>
Jellyfin-Rewind. A "Spotify Wrapped"-like app made for people who use Jellyfin for listening to music!

Jellyfin Rewind 2025 will launch on December 31st 2025.

The rewind feature is updated on December 31 each year to reflect the music statistics for the current year. Currently, the rewind for 2024 is available.  
    
Note: This tool is external to Jellyfin and cannot be directly integrated. Users need to log in with their username and password or API key to access their personalized rewind.

To enhance your rewind experience, it is highly recommended to install the **Playback Reporting** plugin on your Jellyfin server. This plugin tracks your playback history and provides better insights for your rewind. The installation process takes less than 2 minutes and requires admin access.

**Important Tips for Playback Reporting Plugin:**
- By default, the plugin stores only the last 3 months of playback data. It is advised to change this setting to store at least the last two years.
- You can access the settings directly from your Jellyfin server and update the retention period.

Setup Instructions:
1. Select a port during installation. The app works immediately afterward.
2. If you want external access, NGINX Proxy Manager is recommended.

This container is simple to use and provides a standalone service for music playback analysis and summary.
  </Overview>
  <Category>Tools/Utilities</Category>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:80]</WebUI>
  <TemplateURL/>
  <Icon>https://github.com/RichKidsDev/Unraid-Templates/blob/main/jellyfin-rewind/jellyfin-rewind-logo1.png?raw=true</Icon>
  <ExtraParams>--security-opt no-new-privileges:true --pull always</ExtraParams>
  <PostArgs/>
  <CPUset/>
  <DateInstalled>1734800400</DateInstalled>
  <DonateText>Support the Developer</DonateText>
  <DonateLink>https://github.com/sponsors/Chaphasilor</DonateLink>
  <Requires/>
  <Config Name="Host Port 1" Target="80" Default="8080" Mode="tcp" Description="External port mapped to container port 80" Type="Port" Display="always" Required="true" Mask="false">8080</Config>
</Container>
